Zaki Nusseibeh Collection AD.MC.020
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Sheikh Zayed and Nelson Mandela receiving gifts from Emirati girls with Zaki Nusseibeh., 1995; ref136; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Women; Girls; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Airplanes; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Jewelry; Transportation; Political Leadership; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed shaking hands with Nelson Mandela with Zaki Nusseibeh in the background., 1995; ref137; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Flags; Men; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed at a ribbon cutting ceremony., Circa 1970; ref138; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Ceremony; Men; Crowds; Flags; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed waving in front of the entrance of a plane with Zaki Nusseibeh in front., Circa 1970; ref139; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Airplanes; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Transportation; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Ahmed bin Hamid Al-Qubaisi walking with Zaki Nusseibeh in front of Temple of Jupiter in Baalbeck, Lebanon., Circa 1970; ref140; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Baalbek, Lebanon; Roman Architecture; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Sheikhs; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Outdoors; Monuments
- Sheikh Zayed with British officials seated among a crowd watching an eagle with Sheikh Sultan bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, and Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1990; ref141; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Political Leadership; England; Men; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Animals; Birds; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Color Photography; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership; Outdoors
- Sheikh Khalifa with French President Jacques Chirac and Zaki Nusseibeh in front of a falcon statue in Palais de L'Elysée., 21 July 2006; ref142; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Furnishings; Paris, France; Palace; Sheikhs; Color Photography; Men; Political Leadership; Statues; Animals; Birds; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Interiors; Paintings; Statues; Art
- Sheikh Khalifa shaking hands with Zaki Nusseibeh next to policemen., Circa 2000; ref143; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Sheikhs; Police; Uniforms; Color Photography; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh during a a visit to Westminister with Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh Sultan bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed Al Nahyan., 1989; ref144; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Interiors; London, United Kingdom; Color Photography; Men; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Churches; Priests/Clergymen; Religious Clothing; Architecture; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Military/Soldiers; Chandeliers; Religious Sites; Uniforms; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed in the City of London Hall with Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Sheikh Sultan bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, and Zaki Nusseibeh., 1989; ref145; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; London, United Kingdom; Color Photography; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Swords/Knives; Flags; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Men; Women; Royalty; Insignia/Emblem; Armor; Wigs; Military/Soldiers; Interiors; Political Leadership; Swords/Knives; Medals; Carpets/Rugs; Weapons; Political Leadership
- Shekih Zayed walking through Souq Al Markezi (central market)., Circa 1970; ref146; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Markets; Men; Military/Soldiers; Street Vendors; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Uniforms; Fruit/Vegetables; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed walking with a crowd and waving at Souq Al Markezi (central market)., Circa 1970; ref147; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Police; Crowds; Markets; Cars; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Transportation; Buildings; Political Leadership; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed looking at a fabric swatch book at Souq Al Markezi (central market)., Circa 1970; ref148; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Markets; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Insignia/Emblem; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Shops; Hats; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed walking with a crowd at Souq Al Markezi (central market)., Circa 1970; ref149; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Markets; Men; Crowds; Military/Soldiers; Guns; Street Vendors; Uniforms; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Weapons; Buildings; Shops; Political Leadership; Outdoors